kingfisherworld.com 2010-12-13

# Kingfisher World - PRIVACY POLICY

| KINGFISHER World Privacy Policy 2009  
---  
   
KINGFISHER World ("K-World") takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.  
   
**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  
  
  * This Privacy Policy covers K-World's treatment of personally identifiable information that K-World collects when you are on the K-World site, and when you use K-World's services.
  * This policy also covers K-World's treatment of any personally identifiable information that K-World business partners share with K-World. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that UB does not own or control, or to people that UB does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
  
  * K-World collects personally identifiable information when you register for a K-World account, when you use certain K-World services, when you visit K-World pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes . K-World may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
  * When you register (iKING)with K-World we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with K-World and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * K-World also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, K-World cookie information and the page you requested.
  * In addition, when you use K-World's services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
  * K-World uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
  
  * K-World will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * K-World will send personally identifiable information about you to other   
companies or people when:  

    * We have your consent to share the information;
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
    * We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent right to use this information except to respond to your comments or to resolve the service issues.);
    * We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the KINGFISHER World Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Cookies**  
  
  * K-World may set and access K-World cookies on your computer.
  * K-World allows that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to K-World’s cookies.
  * K-World uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with K-World products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
  
  * K-World gives you the ability to edit your K-World Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want K-World to contact you about specials and new products.
  * You may request deletion of your K-World account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Soon you can read here about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Security**  
  
  * Your K-World Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
  * In certain areas K-World uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
  
  * K-World may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions complete a [feedback form](http://kingfisherworld.com/privacy/cgi_feedback) .  

**Download PDF**
